<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="changelog_title">Changelog</string>
    <string name="changelog_dialog">
        &lt;i>Project site: https://github.com/eolme/browser-suze&lt;br>
        Changelog: https://github.com/eolme/browser-suze/blob/master/CHANGELOG.md&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Version: 1.0.0&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA First release
    </string>

    <string name="overview_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="overview_dialog">Here you can access all opened tabs and your data: saved sites on the startpage, bookmarks and history.
        In the settings you can decide which content will be shown at start.</string>

    <string name="startSite_title">Start site</string>
    <string name="startSite_dialog">Long press any saved bookmark to set it as start site. This site will always load on start
        or when you open a new tab. You can also set an blank start page via the bookmark menu.</string>

    <string name="gestures_title">Gestures</string>
    <string name="gestures_dialog">On the toolbar and the Navigation button you can use gestures:   ▪ Swipe up/down → scroll to top/bottom;   ▪ Swipe left/right → navigate back/forward;   ▪ Tap → open the menu;   ▪ Long press → open Fast toggle dialog   You can configure gestures in the settings.</string>

    <string name="fastToggle_title">Fast toggle</string>
    <string name="fastToggle_dialog">If you long press the \"menu\" or the \"Navigation button\" the \"Fast toggle dialog\"
        will open. Here you can change some important settings without leaving the current website. You can also add websites
        to your whitelist for AdBlocker, JavaScript or Cookies..</string>

    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="menu_dialog">Manage your tabs, share or save content, handle the current tab or use some features: just try it.
        The menu can be dismissed, like all other notifications, by clicking back, clicking outside the menu or simply be
        swiping the menu down.</string>

    <string name="not_title">Notifications</string>
    <string name="not_dialog">Notifications are displayed on the bottom of the screen. They can also be dismissed like the
        menus.</string>

    <string name="settings_dialog">There are even more options in the settings. Try it out!</string>

    <string name="license_title">Copyright © 2019 by Petrov Anton</string>
    <string name="license_dialog">
        &lt;i>For more information visit the project site on Github: https://github.com/eolme/browser-suze&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Following open source libraries or projects are used within this software:&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>DynamicGrid&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        askerov&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vTHZH&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Lightning Browser&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Mozilla Public License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Anthony Restaino&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUruk&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Material Design Icons&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1.&lt;br>
        Templarian&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/Templarian/MaterialDesign&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Ninja&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Matthew Lee&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUrEh&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>SimpleEncryptionLib&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        hummatli&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/hummatli/SimpleEncryptionLib</string>

    <string name="cont_dialog">

    </string>

</resources>
